Many people comment that I keep
eating so much and why does it not reflect in my body
?  To be honest,
I myself don't know why it doesn't feel like it in my body.
I keep eating everything as far as food is concerned.
Why do
people think that only fat people are hungry?
We thin people are also very gluttonous.  It's just that it does
n't feel in our body.
Many people also praise my hair a lot by commenting.
I keep cutting my hair
because I like short hair.
My hair does not fall because
I use this shampoo.  Earlier I
also used to use one or two shampoos.  Because of this my
hair fell a lot.  That's why I did
n't feel like keeping long hair.   So that's why
I get my hair cut again and again.
But ever since I have been using this sample,
my hair fall has also stopped.
When I started using it in the beginning,
I got good results.  This
sample is also available on Flipkart and Amazon.
You can go and order everything.
Poha and tea were prepared for evening snack and
I like poha and tea very much.  If I
tell you a secret, this poha has been
made by my husband.  One day he
made poha by mistake.  Since then I told you to make
Poha only because you
make it very tasty.  Aru's father is saying that
I made a mistake by making Poha.
Now you will get this poha made only from me.